<resources>
    <!--    -->
    <string name="app_name">Transsectes APP</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go back</string>
    <string name="Delete">Delete</string>
    <!--    Home View   -->
    <string name="home_how_to">How to do a transect</string>
    <string name="home_start">Start a transect</string>
    <string name="home_records">Transect records</string>
    <string name="home_contact">Contact</string>
    <!--    Contact View -->
    <string name="contact_title">Contact</string>
    <string name="contact_p1">If you observe a turtle on the sand, a track, hatchlings, an injured or dead turtle, or any other incident related to a sea turtle, call:</string>
    <string name="contact_p2">112</string>
    <string name="contact_p3">For any doubts or incidents related to transects or sea turtles, contact:</string>
    <string name="contact_p4">Emergency phone numbers</string>
    <string name="contact_p5">6222651374</string>
    <string name="contact_p6">Visit our website for more information</string>
    <!--    Start a transect View   -->
    <string name="start_enable_gps">Enable GPS service and go back</string>
    <string name="start_gps_disabled">GPS service is disabled</string>
    <string name="start_gps_background_title">GPS background service disabled</string>
    <string name="start_gps_background_p1">Please go to app settings (OS) and enable GPS service to 'ALWAYS' and relaunch the app</string>
    <string name="start_start">Start a transect</string>
    <string name="start_stop">Stop a transect</string>
    <string name="start_add_new">Add new marks</string>
    <string name="start_add_new_button">Add new geopoint</string>
    <string name="start_stop_title">Fill in the following fields</string>
    <string name="start_stop_question1">Has the tractor passed?</string>
    <string name="start_stop_question2">Number of informers</string>
    <string name="start_stop_question3">Observations</string>
    <string name="start_stop_note_title">Note:</string>
    <string name="start_stop_note_p1">If you want to continue with the current transect, you must press the button at the top left to go back.</string>
    <string name="start_stop_note_p2">If you press the 'cancel' button, all data regarding the current transect will be lost.</string>
    <string name="start_stop_note_p3">If you press the 'send' button, the data for the current transect will be sent (saved), and you can start a new transect.</string>
    <string name="start_stop_cancel_title">Cancel transect</string>
    <string name="start_stop_cancel_p1">If you continue (delete), the information will be lost and cannot be recovered.</string>
    <string name="start_stop_send_title">Save transect</string>
    <string name="start_stop_send_p1">If you continue (save), the information will be saved and cannot be modified.</string>
    <!--    Transect Records View   -->
    <string name="records_transects">Transects</string>
    <string name="records_all_transects">All transects</string>
    <string name="records_download">Download</string>
    <string name="records_remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="records_remove_button">Remove all transects</string>
    <string name="records_remove_p1">This action cannot be undone, be careful.</string>
    <!--    GePeC Info  -->
    <string name="gepec_info_website">https://gepec.cat</string>
    <string name="gepec_info_email_especies">especies@gepec.cat</string>
    <string name="gepec_info_email_voluntariat">voluntariat@gepec.cat</string>
    <!--    How to  -->
    <string name="how2_title">How to make a transect</string>
    <string name="how2_1_title">Transects</string>
    <string name="how2_1_p1">Surveys involve conducting patrols along the beach to detect possible traces of turtle nesting during the period between June 1st and October 31st.</string>
    <string name="how2_1_p2">It is recommended to carry out these patrols between 22:00 and 08:00 the following day, although the early hours of the night are the most suitable for this.</string>
    <string name="how2_2_title">What are we looking for?</string>
    <string name="how2_2_p1">When a turtle emerges from the sea onto the beach to nest, it crawls using its flippers as if they were legs. This movement leaves a very distinctive track ascending towards the beach.</string>
    <string name="how2_2_p2">When it finds a suitable place, it digs the nest, lays the eggs, covers it, and returns to the sea, leaving a track with the same characteristics as the ascent but in the direction of the sea, often with a line in the middle to drag a tube through which the eggs have come out.</string>
    <string name="how2_3_title">What are we looking for?</string>
    <string name="how2_3_p1">An even greater challenge would be encountering hatchlings between August and October, emerging from undetected nests and walking on the sand towards the sea. This is extremely unlikely, as they hatch at night and are very small.</string>
    <string name="how2_3_p2">If we find small hatchlings or a large turtle alive or dead outside the water, we should quickly call:</string>
    <string name="how2_3_p3">112</string>
    <string name="how2_4_title">Lighting</string>
    <string name="how2_4_p1">You can bring a flashlight or a headlamp with a red light, although it is rarely necessary for walking. We will use it if we are unsure about something during the transect, but moonlight is usually sufficient. Whenever possible, keep the flashlight off and walk quietly. If we do not have enough light to observe tracks, we will hold the flashlight with our arm extended towards the ground to highlight the sand and relief better. Never point the flashlight towards the water, as it could scare off a turtle if one is trying to come ashore.</string>
    <string name="how2_4_p2">You can put red cellophane paper on a flashlight or in front of the mobile phone flashlight.</string>
    <string name="how2_5_title">Sensitization</string>
    <string name="how2_5_p1">We can take advantage of the walk to inform and raise awareness among people or groups we encounter on the beach (athletes, families, anglers, and others) to help us by calling 112 if they witness nesting or find tracks. Always at our discretion and willingness.</string>
    <string name="how2_6_title">Start a transect</string>
    <string name="how2_6_p1">We will start a transect in a specific area of the beach and activate the "START TRANSECT" button.</string>
    <string name="how2_6_p2">We will walk along the beach, by the seashore, observing the first meters of the undulating dry sand.</string>
    <string name="how2_7_title">Finish transect</string>
    <string name="how2_7_p1">Once we finish our route, we will access the "START TRANSECT" section and press "STOP TRANSECT", which will take us to a screen where we must fill in the following fields. If we find the beach plowed by a machine that could erase the tracks, we will record the number of people informed, note interesting observations, etc., and send the data.</string>

</resources>
